[{"content":"Name: Dr. Shaheen M Hussaini MD Facility:","entities":[[6,31,"PERSON"]]},{"content":"Name: Dr. Cosette M Stahl DO Facility:","entities":[[6,28,"PERSON"]]},{"content":"Name: Dr. Shaheen M Hussaini MD Facility:","entities":[[6,31,"PERSON"]]},{"content":"Name: Dr. Lori L Barr MD Facility:","entities":[[6,24,"PERSON"]]},{"content":"Name: Austin Radiological Association, Inc Facility: North Austin Medical Center","entities":[[6,42,"ORG"]]},{"content":"Of: 11/13/2020","entities":[[4,14,"DATE"]]},{"content":"$0.00","entities":[[0,5,"MONEY"]]},{"content":"1/12/2012 6/28/2018 2/14/2020 6/28/2018","entities":[[0,9,"DATE"]]},{"content":"Date 6/28/2018 M Hussaini *** 7/25/2018 M Stahl DO *** 1/1/2015 L Barr MD *** 4/5/2018 Association, *** Claims _CPLXReports","entities":[[78,86,"DATE"]]},{"content":"Date 6/28/2018 Description: 6/28/2018 Description: 6/28/2018 Description: 6/28/2018 Description: TDC cuimexp_ext_Daily_byPolyr_RateSt_CLMX","entities":[[5,14,"DATE"]]},{"content":"Date 6/28/2018 Description: 6/28/2018 Description: 6/28/2018 Description: 6/28/2018 Description: TDC cuimexp_ext_Daily_byPolyr_RateSt_CLMX","entities":[[5,14,"DATE"]]},{"content":"Date 6/28/2018 Description: 6/28/2018 Description: 6/28/2018 Description: 6/28/2018 Description: TDC cuimexp_ext_Daily_byPolyr_RateSt_CLMX","entities":[[5,14,"DATE"]]},{"content":"Date 6/28/2018 Description: 6/28/2018 Description: 6/28/2018 Description: 6/28/2018 Description: TDC cuimexp_ext_Daily_byPolyr_RateSt_CLMX","entities":[[5,14,"DATE"]]},{"content":"Eff Date 6/28/2018 Name: Description: 6/28/2018 Name: Description: 6/28/2018 Name: Description: 6/28/2018 Name: Description: TDC Data cuimexp_ext_Daily_byPolyr_RateSt_CLMX","entities":[[9,18,"DATE"]]},{"content":"Eff Date 6/28/2018 Name: Description: 6/28/2018 Name: Description: 6/28/2018 Name: Description: 6/28/2018 Name: Description: TDC Data cuimexp_ext_Daily_byPolyr_RateSt_CLMX","entities":[[9,18,"DATE"]]},{"content":"Eff Date 6/28/2018 Name: Description: 6/28/2018 Name: Description: 6/28/2018 Name: Description: 6/28/2018 Name: Description: TDC Data cuimexp_ext_Daily_byPolyr_RateSt_CLMX","entities":[[9,18,"DATE"]]},{"content":"Eff Date 6/28/2018 Name: Description: 6/28/2018 Name: Description: 6/28/2018 Name: Description: 6/28/2018 Name: Description: TDC Data cuimexp_ext_Daily_byPolyr_RateSt_CLMX","entities":[[9,18,"DATE"]]},{"content":"Date 2/13/2019 Association, Inc fracture) 2/13/2019 Association, Inc 3/18/2019 Association, Inc 4/9/2019 _CPLXReports cuimexp_ext_Daily_byPolyr_RateSt_CLMX","entities":[[5,14,"DATE"]]},{"content":"Date 2/13/2019 Association, Inc fracture) 2/13/2019 Association, Inc 3/18/2019 Association, Inc 4/9/2019 _CPLXReports cuimexp_ext_Daily_byPolyr_RateSt_CLMX","entities":[[5,14,"DATE"]]},{"content":"Date 2/13/2019 Association, Inc fracture) 2/13/2019 Association, Inc 3/18/2019 Association, Inc 4/9/2019 _CPLXReports cuimexp_ext_Daily_byPolyr_RateSt_CLMX","entities":[[96,104,"DATE"]]},{"content":"$22,710.48 $0.00 $792.00 $1,748.00","entities":[[25,34,"MONEY"]]},{"content":"Reserve $22,710.48 $0.00 $792.00 $1,748.00","entities":[[19,24,"MONEY"]]},{"content":"$22,710.48 $0.00 $792.00 $1,748.00","entities":[[17,24,"MONEY"]]},{"content":"$2,450.00 $0.00 $1,783.00 $1,783.00","entities":[[16,25,"MONEY"]]},{"content":"$2,450.00 $0.00 $1,783.00 $1,783.00","entities":[[0,9,"MONEY"]]},{"content":"8/15/2018","entities":[[0,9,"DATE"]]},{"content":"4/5/2018","entities":[[0,8,"DATE"]]},{"content":"7/25/2018","entities":[[0,9,"DATE"]]},{"content":"15,966.04","entities":[[0,9,"MONEY"]]},{"content":"75,965.04","entities":[[0,9,"MONEY"]]},{"content":"for A-MMED Ambulance Inc., DBA A-Med Carrier: Certain Underwriters at Lloyds - Certain","entities":[[5,25,"ORG"]]},{"content":"roticy Claim Type Status ALAE Paid Date Date Date Date Date State y yP ated Paid Reserves","entities":[[0,6,"WORK_OF_ART"]]},{"content":"30,000.00","entities":[[0,9,"MONEY"]]},{"content":"07/11/11","entities":[[0,8,"DATE"]]},{"content":"Arvin Taneja","entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"]]},{"content":"Status Rate Specialt Claim Type Status Litig Indemnity ALAE Paid Total Case yP","entities":[[0,78,"WORK_OF_ART"]]},{"content":"exps_paid: $3,583.50","entities":[[11,20,"MONEY"]]},{"content":"total_incurred: 600,000.00\n","entities":[[16,26,"MONEY"]]},{"content":"Flower Villa Inc","entities":[[0,16,"ORG"]]},{"content":"Long Beach Care Center Inc","entities":[[0,26,"ORG"]]},{"content":"ALF at Stuart LLC","entities":[[0,17,"ORG"]]},{"content":"Hofer, Annamarie","entities":[[0,16,"PERSON"]]},{"content":"Olsen, Doris","entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"]]},{"content":"BURKHART, WILLIAM","entities":[[0,17,"PERSON"]]},{"content":"Flower Villa Inc","entities":[[0,16,"ORG"]]},{"content":"FUKUSHIMA, YUKIO","entities":[[0,16,"PERSON"]]},{"content":"Long Beach Care Center Inc","entities":[[0,26,"ORG"]]},{"content":"Verna Bennett","entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"]]},{"content":"Richard P. Williams","entities":[[0,19,"PERSON"]]},{"content":"","entities":[]}]